[Music]
thank you
it's almost time sleet The Faded day has
come at last what we have been planning
all these years the day we killed Dr
Robotnik and retake our freedom dingo
shut up I'm trying to watch my Yukio AMV
[Music]
wait kill Robotnik what the [__] are you
talking about we never discussed this
[__]
sleep you know when I say we I mean the
voices in my own head like the one that
sounds like the Joker
dingo we can't kill Robotnik why would
we even want to
sometimes when we are extra good he
gives us meatloaf
it's already nine in the morning why
aren't you and your cute little maid
uniforms does daddy need to spank a
[__]
[Music]
sleigh come look the next door neighbors
bought the water slide no way really
[Music]
Dr Robotnik can we get waters lied to it
looks like fun of course not I'm evil
evil people aren't supposed to have fun
look at those peasants so innocent and
naive
[Music]
it makes my blood boil even more than
when I see a woman in positions of power
they think they're happy just cause
they're free they should be under my
absolute rule like YouTube [__] god
it feels so good being evil
I'm hungry I'm going to Olive Garden
but Dr robotnixer you can't afford to
wait at Olive Garden I know that's why
I'm just going to eat a handful of their
Unlimited Supply of free breadsticks
before going to the Arby's next door and
then I will get a couple roast beef
sandwiches from there instead you two
had better have the house clean before I
get back
if that puddle of dingo's pee is still
in the garage by the time I get back you
are both going without dinner
thank you
good evening Dr Robotnik isn't it so
great being here in the land of the free
and Home of the Brave the great United
States of America where absolutely
nobody is evil
[Music]
thank you
can I have 16 roast beef sandwiches
damn
[Music]
haha I'm just pulling your balls 16
roasty sandwiches is a lot go you must
be having a huge get together with your
friends and family aren't you
yeah that's it actually can you raise it
up to 29 Rose beasts and witches there's
going to be a lot of us and don't forget
the extra mayonnaise and grilled onions
[Music]
thank you
another Saturday night is just another
lonely night for the master of evil
maybe I should save a couple sandwiches
for sleet and dingo
peeing out of your fat balls and helped
me clean the bathroom
foreign
this sucks it seems like every day
Robotnik is becoming more and more
demanding than ever will we ever be free
of this life of slavery
sleet you're poking on your tears again
you should go drink some water don't
tell me what to do
[Music]
there just has to be a way for us to
escape this wretched place under
robotnik's rule
maybe we could fake our deaths or
something and make a run for it after he
throws our supposedly dead corpses in
the trash can outside no waitrobot Nick
is into necrophilia isn't he he'll
probably still keep us around or we
could just walk down the street and not
come back Dinko that's the most stupid
[__] you ever said Robot Nick always
locks the door on his way out so we
can't run away
but he left the door open this time
all right
foreign
[Music]
do you got everything
I think so
we don't have much do we we've never had
much
yeah
this is for making the Slick sour cream
off your nipples for all those years
[Music]
this is for all the poop stuff you made
me do
Robotnik never made us do poop stuff I
was talking to you dingface now come on
let's go
[Music]
how about I suck your fat [__] mutts
as celebration for finally getting out
of there
we should stay at a friend's house for
the time being so that Robotnik can't
find us and drag us back but we don't
have any friends haha oh yeah that's
right
[Music]
do you think we made the right decision
just a band leaving without a plan how
else will we ever get to live normal
lives we're not exactly good people we
can't just expect to live normal lives
sleep look a guitar it looks all beat up
did it fall out of one of those Mexican
bouncy cars do you remember when I
traded my Beanie Baby collection for
that guitar after graduation he wanted
to be just like Hannah Montana's ad
Billy Ray Cyrus from the Disney Channel
no I wanted to be [__] by him okay we
need to figure out where we're going to
stay for the night we can't just
foreign
[Music]
there's many a young boy who feels
things he can't comprehend
[Music]
I don't like it when a cowboy has
feelings
well the cowboy May brag about things
that he's done with his women this town
ain't big enough for the two of us but
the ones that bragged loudest are the
ones that are most likely queer
Cowboys
[Music]
for each other
do you think all them Saddles and Boots
was about where are you boys trying to
hit and there's many a cowboy who don't
understand the way that he feels for his
brother
boy
if you can't comprehend
[Music]
Hotel don't like it when a cowboy has
feelings for men
[Music]
sleet thing go are either of you still
awake I have a roast beef sandwich left
if you wanted I had sex full sandwiches
left while I was walking up the driveway
but I shoved five of them up my ass I
mean I dropped them on the ground just
one bite though cause I want most of it
I'm still hungry
listen I know you two are mad at me for
making you wear those stupid made
uniforms it's just dingo looked so sexy
in it and sleet
well yours was part of a two-for-one
deal I guess what I'm trying to say is I
though about how I've been treating you
these past few years I treated you more
like my personal [__] when really I
should have treated you like well like
my best friends because that's what you
are
the three of us together we're like the
Jackson 5 but there's only three of us
and Michael Jackson isn't here I guess
every time we watch The Jackson 5
together which is every Tuesday night at
exactly 9 pm I can't help but think
about how they're so much like us it
makes me feel like a total badass and
[__]
are you two [__] listening to me you
answer me when I'm talking to you
[__]
those [__] escaped I'll get you two if
it's the last thing I do before I die of
diabetes
thank you
today's Friday and we stole mom's car
while she was taking a [__] we are
taking it for a joyride haha we're so
bad feet underground by now Sonia are
you recording put the phone away but I
wanna put this on Tick Tock Knuckles
sorry for all the noise Sonic and
manokar fighting again my girlfriend
Mindy is always out there getting [__]
in the ass by other guys
are you done then or are you going to
continue calling my girlfriend a [__]
I'm only telling it like it is you
started it by saying Mindy's a better
lover to you then my sweet sweet Bart
Levy is to me and we all know that's
[__] because Bartleby is a million
times better than your [__] girl
you're just jealous and you're just a
[__] that's why you're too scared to
fight now
Knuckles was right
man up and fight me gunky poops
hello hello
that's it get out of the [__] car are
you gonna drag me out yes I will [__]
get out of the [__] car holy
[__] what the [__] [__]
get out are you gonna drag me out get
out are you gonna drag me out I said get
the [__] out of the car are you gonna
track me out if I don't get out don't
touch me what are you gonna do about it
don't touch me can I pop your seatbelt I
can get my own seat belt
welcome on gunky poose pop it off
don't touch me how about you don't touch
me instead if you can't touch me then
how come I'm not allowed to touch you
because Bartleby has more money than you
don't touch me [__] if I wanna touch
you I'll touch you
[__] don't you [__] touch me
I will [__] your ass up
guys we're in a neighborhood
what if they call the cops
bartlebby would dump him bartlebby would
bail me out you're not supposed to have
the car what if somebody calls the cops
don't [__] with me I will beat your ass
we should go somewhere else my nail
[__] hurts that's cool what was that
I said that's cool guys seriously
I'm tired hold on [__] you do get tired
quickly the next time we walk somewhere
can I walk in front of you guys you
wouldn't believe how much your butt
cheek smell downwind oh my God Sonic
look over there isn't that your
boyfriend
bartlevy Montclair rubbed Dresden who is
world famous for being the richest and
sexiest man in the entire world no
the entire universe
oh my God it is him I look all trashy I
should have worn something better I
didn't think he was dropping by today
you look great Sonic oh no oh my God
Bartleby is coming this way
what do I say you guys I didn't take a
bath so I smell really bad Sonia do my
spines look nice bro it's like your
dignity goes away every time you see
your boyfriend don't embarrass me bro
laughs
up hi Bartleby my lover how are you
doing this fine evening haha Sonic
you're blushing damn eyebrows butt
cheeks are about to rip out of his pants
somebody find some duct tape do you want
to come inside me and my Subs just got
home but mum should almost be finished
making dinner
do you like Little Caesar's five dollar
hot and ready pizzas my mom said she was
thinking about ordering one of those
mom we're home is it okay if my
boyfriend Bart lovey eats with us
welcome home Sonic
Michael Jackson what are you doing here
in my house oh I was just passing
through the neighborhood and decided to
stop by and see how your boys were doing
the you kids are which of you thought it
would be fun to take my car around for a
joyride speak up now and make it clear
to Mommy who's getting their ass beat
it was Maddox idea no it was Sonics that
was a trick question you bozos both of
you are getting the blame here do you
know how worried your uncle and I were
when we saw the car was missing and
Michael Jackson was standing right out
front with none of you kids anywhere to
be seen what if Michael Jackson abducted
your sister and you got her into trouble
Evans Alina I would never do something
like that she's a girl
foreign
that's because I wanted to make my
advice with the kids when they got home
we're sorry Uncle Chuck
sorry Michael Jackson I was quite all
right Buzz the fact that I get to stand
this close to you where I can see the
perfect outline of your 15 year old
penis has already made this whole night
worth it
nobody used the bathroom on the ground
floor for quite some time
it's so stinky in there that you would
think George Bush flew another plane
into the World Trade Centers haha
mom what is Knuckles great grandfather
Affair doing here I don't know I forgot
Knuckles kicked me out of the house
after he caught me mixing
enough sleeping pills to kill him into
his bowl of SpaghettiOs and said I
couldn't go back home until I had time
to think about the consequences of my
action
yeah that
now who the [__] could that be I'll get
it
did you just see that what the [__] are
sleep and dingo doing here bro you know
I don't know things
foreign
please
Robotnik isn't hiding in the bushes to
stab me with a knife is he I'm not in
the mood to deal with him tonight no no
we just really just want to come and
that's all
what are you doing still talking to them
my blue cheeked up bro we don't
associate ourselves with evil people no
but that's the thing you see we we don't
want to be evil anymore we want to put
that entire life behind us who ran away
from Robotnik but now we need a place to
hide for a little while because we know
he's going to come looking for us I'm
going to set the table for dinner you
kids sort this out yourselves
oh my God sleet it's Michael Jackson
from the Jackson 5.
[Music]
I haven't been hogged by anybody over
the age of six years old and so long are
you a fan of me too sleep well no not
since the allegations
sleet have you guys really changed I
mean we want to try that's what matters
right
so can we please stay here just for one
night I promise we won't be a burden on
you
you know this moment in time reminds me
of Sonic Underground episode 7 the price
of Freedom where Mindy's dad was
building those weird spider watches or
some [__] that would spy on people and
steal their information but Mindy's dad
learned right from wrong he helped us
reprogrammed the spider watches to try
and kill you and dingo instead I think
if Mindy's Dad could change well then
maybe you guys can too
thank you Sonic I can't see why the
Sonic Underground band is named after
you instead of one of your siblings
you're really cool
[Music]
dingo look it's the Hedgehog families
Royal scepter
I bet we could steal that [__] after
everybody else goes to bed but sleet
were not evil anymore only evil people
steal things oh yeah
[Music]
foreign
what what are you looking at
why are you making that face at me stop
it
everybody gets one slice
oh look at that Little Caesars Pizza how
extravagant what are you trying to say
[__] mommy calm down you're using the
No-No words again all I'm saying is that
you didn't even get Papa John's since
you knew you were having guests over I
would think you would at least be
accommodating except I didn't know
anybody was coming over wasn't Papa John
fired for saying the n-word during an
employee training call yeah but his
pizza is still bitching you know I think
Papa John is a cool guy if you ask me I
think he should be allowed to say the
n-word why are only black people allowed
to say it
because that word has history bro it
means something different if a white
person says it then if a black person
says it but isn't what you said just now
contradictory you said yourself the word
has history shouldn't it be our
generation's job to reclaim the word and
rewrite its history
so that future Generations can't say
God [__] damn it Sonia
can you shut the [__] up oh my God what
the hell
[Applause]
what what did I say you just said the
n-word [__] yes cause that's what we're
talking about isn't it well we've all
been saying n-word instead not the
actual word you just dropped the word
itself like how a good old us of a drop
that bomb on the city based off hope
Panda Express listen all I'm saying is
we should be able to say [__] without
restriction if we let people dictate how
we speak we are no different than the
Nazi pretty under Adolf well then Amen
to and Frank that [__] really knew how
to write a diary in the Attic am I right
now how about we eat our pizza well that
just begs the question then why would
you want to use the n-word without
restriction in the first place unless
you're a racist at that point it would
be best if white people stop using the
word altogether
new hairs I think marrying a seeking
your own boy should be made legal in all
50 states of America
okay that's enough Michael Jackson so up
sleet dingo why don't you I'm the
contrary side what I'm saying will never
be enough my words alone cannot make
[__] five-year-old posts legal like
it should be for ethical reasons all our
voices must be heard together it needs
to be a team effort so tell us about
yourselves the real sleep and tinko what
are the real you like well sometimes I
Dr Robotnik says we are not allowed to
have passions of Our Own but Robotnik
isn't here right well no I guess not so
go on then I suppose Robotnik can't hit
me if he's not here right yes that's
right okay it's a little embarrassing
but um sometimes I uh
it's okay take your time sometimes I
like to collect marbles that sounds
kinda gay dingo I want to go home
then hurry and those so that we may be
rid of you fog yet
excuse me everyone I must say something
I can't adjust it idly by any longer why
The Devout Christian man I'm forced to
share a table and eat a Little Caesars
five dollars hot and ready pizza with
sinners
what are you trying to say
I am saying what we are all thinking
Bible verse 18 22 of the Holy Bible
states that man shall not lie with a man
as one does with a [__]
all the lust Sinners will be dealt with
the punishment of Eternal damnation
the fires of Hell will consume you
unless you take God's hand into Eternal
salvation and stop getting [__] in the
ass
isn't the Bible written by the hand of
man not God of course not what dare you
speak such nonsense I mean it kind of
was written by men but like a white man
so it's got to be true the purple [__]
speaks the truth in the eyes of God to
be born days hardly any different than
being born as a [__] or as a black
person
oh how rapidly the the thousands were
healed
Lord
that's what the Earth does around the
Sun you know the sun can never burn up
because it creates its own energy which
then Burns and creates its own energy
foreign
first met we were about your age
we met in school while we were both a
part of the planetary Exchange program
here on Earth
I thought dingo was really annoying back
then I mean I still do sometimes even
now
but it's not the same kind of annoying
he's an idiot sure but he's my idiot and
he's loving and kind
way too kind to just waste his days as a
bounty hunter under Robotnik
we both joined Dr robot Nick to try and
find our place in life and now I wonder
if it was a mistake so big we'll never
be able to go back on it we've been tied
to him for so long people will only ever
associate us with him your friends don't
like us I can't tell and I bet they
never will
I don't think it's ever too late to find
your place in life's lead did you know
my brother was a part of the vicious Rat
Patrol an old Thief group until he
changed his ways and I believe I made a
lot of embarrassing mistakes too that's
my lover Bartleby had to clean up for me
our faults and the kinds of people we
keep around us for long periods of time
don't make us who we are you and dingo
will find your place together
don't give up hope
find our place together
but what kind of place is there for us I
wonder
what are you boys doing out here Michael
Jackson Don't Start the gang bang
without me
listen to me sleep sometimes the
youngest people have to make the most
difficult choices
it's like when children have to choose
to either run through the hallway we
have a lot of cameras or to go through
the sacred crawl space to get out of my
bedroom
term Italy the world isn't fair like
that it's not always a wonderful place
you see unlike my Neverland Ranch where
children can write on a Merry-Go-Round
and [__] and then I force them back to
my bedroom to sleep in my bed with me
how old are you sleep I don't know like
40 something oh
[Music]
let's go inside too it's getting late
do you guys think sleep tantingo have
really changed their ways
I doubt it I fully expect us to go
downstairs tomorrow morning and see
everything in the house has been stolen
and then mama is gonna throw a fit and
starts screaming at us yeah and then
Uncle Chuck is going to beat mom for
letting it happen and we'll have to call
the cops on him again nobody cares what
you think Sonia you're a girl besides
bro M and robotnikar hours warn enemies
even if they did change why should we
forgive them
I don't know it's just I wonder if we
can give him the benefit of the doubt it
would be nice if they could be friends
don't you think
no not really
shut up Sonia you're a girl
will you three shut up I'm trying to go
firstly sorry Bartleby me and my Subs
will go to bed soon good night manic
good night Sonia night bro night Sonic
night manic good night sis
good night boys I hope you have the
sweetest dreams tonight where you flee
around like Peter Pan and freeway to
Neverland to Eternal happiness where you
will be you forever
good night Michael Jack good night
Michael night Michael Jackson
good night music and Sonic good night
Bartleby hey ha just the boys aren't you
going to say goodnight to me too Michael
Jackson no Michael Jackson do you think
you can go downstairs
what do you think I'm going to try and
touch one of you both while you're
asleep yes you're so silly I woke her
downstairs lock the door on your way out
oh
you know sleet I had a lot of fun
tonight how so just sitting around the
dinner table with friends sharing
interests this is the most fun I've had
in months that's the kind of thing we
could never do with Robotnik normally
during dinner time he sits at the table
alone and throws food on the floor for
us to fight over completely naked after
he starts us for weeks dingo shut up I'm
trying to sleep
I guess tonight was kinda cool
foreign
I finally found you [__]
[Music]
Michael Jackson
come on
what the hell is going on down here it's
Dr Robotnik he's finally come to kill us
he shot Michael Jackson Dr Robotnik
[__] shot Michael Jackson and Michael
Jackson sure does got some fat butt
cheeks
dingo what are you still doing over
there grab your things and come on but
what about Michael Jackson and the
others
who cares about those losers leave them
I won't
Dinko I won't ask again get your fat ass
over here don't make me count down from
10 that won't even work I'm so stupid I
can't comprehend numbers you're the one
who said we're not going to be evil
anymore and leaving your friends to die
is one of the most evil things someone
can do
what but I I mean I'm not
it's just that you're the only one here
I really care about okay why don't you
get that that's why I'm telling you to
get over here right now
single
oh my God sleet from the hit TV show
Sonic Underground is [__] dead a not
a big loss who wants to bet that he's
going to hell sleet
why sleet why why would you give up your
own life to protect me I'm the useless
one I can't even drink a glass of water
without using both hands if either of us
was supposed to die it should be me
nobody would miss me
foreign
[Music]
wake up I said wake up why are you
ignoring me you dumb [__]
sleepy [__] wake the [__] up don't you
understand that I can't live without you
you had your chance you could have
continued being my cute little [__]
but you made your choice and left just
like how Naruto Uzumaki never gave up on
Sasuke Uchiha after he ran away from the
hidden Leaf Village I will never stop
chasing you but I will do what Naruto
should have done to Sasuke I will kill
you instead of be really [__]
homosexual
you you're only like this because you
have nobody who loves you I don't need
anybody to love me those who say they
love you will always leave after they
get tired of you Robotnik my own son of
all people that I thought would support
me I would think it would be you don't
even bother coming to the show tomorrow
but Dad don't hate at me you're not my
son anymore your hair looks like a
[__] peanut okay Boomer
yes there is no such thing as love among
evil people love always becomes hate
you and sleep are the same just think
about how many times sleet has spank you
Dingo and I don't mean the [__] kind of
spanking you don't understand [__] sleep
ain't that fault ain't argued but we
love each other
stop bro this isn't our fight manic is
Right Sonic let's go into the kitchen
and throw some breakfast burritos in the
microwave
[Music]
I'll give you one more chance dingo only
because I'm really [__] nice come
back to my side [__] you [__] then you
will die oh
[__] why are you defending dingo we've
always hated Bingo he's a [__] [__]
you only look at things in black and
white Doctor Robotnik good and evil but
somebody recently taught me that life
shouldn't be that simple
I will keep thinko safe
because while he is a [__] he's
maritard
where did this power come from the
energy source for the Hedgehog Royal
sector comes from the strength of the
holder's emotions and desire to protect
it's a defense mechanism to make sure
those with evil intentions will never be
able to use its power but Mana you have
always been so weak with it kids you
Mother's been devoid of emotion for the
past 15 years but we were born 15 years
ago
I used to be so strong I was the leader
of the resistance fighting against
Robotnik what has changed in me
I can't always rely on others to be
strong for me especially bartlebby
[Music]
but if what Mom said is true then my
love poor Bartleby my feelings for my
lover and the power of bardonic will
make me Unstoppable there's nothing left
Ford lingo and if we stay by you anymore
Dr Robotnik
foreign
[Music]
I want to be
my [__] house robot [__] you oh [__]
you
that's it it's time for me to finally
live up to the title of this video I Dr
Robotnik has had enough
[Applause]
you know what fine leave if that's what
you really want I don't care
but just know that when you do you will
lose the best friend you ever had
I'm going to count down from 10. if you
open the door I'll apologize and we can
forget this ever happened but if I get
up to 10 I'll walk away and you'll never
have to see me again
one two three four five six actually
seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
thirteen fourteen fifteen
15-minute intermission
how about you go away before I come
outside and rape you [__]
[Music]
okay it's morning which means everybody
who doesn't live here get away from my
house
I would like to apologize for my
rudeness we don't care go away I can see
what Knuckles meant when he called me a
boomer after throwing me out of the
house for trying to put enough sleeping
pills into his bowl of SpaghettiOs to
kill him I see now that I may really be
a boomer and maybe sometimes I'm even
[__] [__] but I seen I I
shouldn't be that way to everybody I
understand that nothing will tear you
apart or stand in your way and I respect
that except for the devil who you will
definitely meet in Hell by the way
you truly have a humorous way of going
about things don't you what I would give
to suck your fat [__] Godly nuts
right now or let you sit on my face why
you fart in my mouth
it's my great grandson did you have fun
at the sleepover great grandfather at
there no take me home right now
no [__] way it's Papa John himself
what are you doing here let's just say a
certain king of pop music hit me up over
the phone and told me we got a couple of
cool white people who aren't afraid to
sing it's real cool and I think that
deserves a free slice of pizza king of
Pop Michael Jackson did you call him ah
what can I say paper John he's [__]
racist and probably wants me to eat just
for being black but he has some damn
good pizza you know you were really cool
you looked so strong was I it's only
because I was thinking of you yes but
you know it's supposed to be my job to
protect you I'll have to punish you
later today meet me at my 700 trillion
dollar mansion at exactly 3 30 p.m for
your spanking oh gosh
so sleet where are we going to go now
you know dingo after I was shot
everything went dark I couldn't see a
thing but in my head I could still hear
all the [__] other people were saying
about me and for a second I didn't want
to wake up but then through the darkness
I I saw a face
heading face so I don't know where we're
going to go but we'll find a place we'll
be fine as long as we're together
[Music]
thank you
there we go
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you